Workers United Memorabilia 6284 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Workers United Memorabilia
2009-2009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Workers United
6284 MB
4.94 cubic feet
4.9 linear ft.
Memorabilia.
7123207
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 18, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6284: Workers United Records 6284 AV: Workers United Audiovisual Materials 6284 G: Workers United Posters 6284 P: Workers United Photographs 6284 PUBS: Workers United Publications 6284(d): Workers United Records (digital)
Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union; Service Employees International Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization); Workers United
7123207
- Wooden block - "Workers United, March 21, 2009"; signed (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Secretary/Treasurer Convention Badge - Edgar Romney name badge (Box 1, Folder 2)
- NY Metropolitan Area Joint Board UNITE HERE - application for membership (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Assorted Awards, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  Metro New York, Labor Communications Council First Award; Second Award; Third Award; International Labor communications Association Third Award; Honorable Mention; Second Award
- Assorted information cards (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Save the date card for Centennial Commemoration Workers United/SEIU; Triangle Fire Memorial and Historical Association; Triangle Fire Memorial Design Competition; We Shall Never Forget Remember the Triangle Fire; When women pursue Justice: an exhibition; Cake (Collecting Action and Knowledge about the Everyday); Women of hope; Birds on fire; The New York City Triangle Factor Fire
- Assorted advertisement material, 2005-2011 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  UNITE Local 23-25 (mini calendar); key chain type cards (stiff paper, look like flags) UNITE! Proudly Made in New York; UNITE HERE! Single card calendars (2005-2006); Calendar from American Society of Safety Engineers 'Celebrating 100 Years of Safety'
- Sewing kits (Box 1, Folder 7)
  UNITE!; ILGWU (2)
- Workers United paperweight - Founder's Award - December 6, 2013, Chinatown YMCA (Box 1, Folder 8)
  clear with a hand drawn and colored picture inside
- Baseball cap - 1911 Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire 2011 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  black cap with gold and red lettering
- Sash - Red with gold lettering in both English and Chinese Character - TO: Local 23-25 100 Years Anniversary (opposite end) FROM: Local 23-25 UNITE Retirees (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Sash (two of them) - Red with gold lettering, both English and Chinese Characters - TO: Local 23-25 100 Years Anniversary; FROM: C.L.U.W. Chinese Committee (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Sash - Red with gold lettering - all in Chinese Characters (Box 2, Folder 3)
- UNITE, ILGWU Memorabilia (Box 3, Folder 1)
  ILGWU keychain; UNITE! Pins (24); UNITE! Activist Pin; ILGWU Pin (bedazzled with white stones); I am a proud member of the Workers United Retirees Association Pin (8)
- Hand held signs; 1 Union Health Center ruler (Box 3, Folder 2)
  signs: UNITE HERE!; Worker's United SEIU; Local 23-25 UNITE 100 Years (2); Greetings from UNITE
- Crayon drawings - Day Care (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Triangle Fire Open Museum booklets and pin (Box 4, Folder 1)
  3 mini booklets, 1 pin
- Display panels - "About the Triangle Fire" (Box 4, Folder 2)
  came housed in a clear plastic box, which was dismantled
- Display panels - "About the Triangle Fire" (Box 4, Folder 3)
  came housed in a clear plastic box which was dismantled
- Display panels - "About the Triangle Fire" (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Poster - "Over decades, workers in the garment industry have fashioned a way of life through their union. Their story is a chapter in mankind's long struggle for human dignity. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  29.5x46
- Vinyl banner - White with red and black lettering -- AB Amalgamated Bank (47"x47") (Box 6, Folder 1)
- T-shirt - Black with yellow lettering -- Front: ? / Back: GOTTA CLUW? (Box 7, Folder 1)
- T-shirt - White with black and red lettering - Front: CLUW / Back: We didn't come here to swap recipes:not Then-1974; not Now-1999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- T-shirt - White with blue and peach design - Front: Women Labor's Future - Coalition of Labor Union Women / Back: [blank] (Box 7, Folder 3)
- T-shirt - Black with purple and red design - Front: Vision Voices Votes / Back: [blank] (Box 7, Folder 4)
- T-shirt - Black with white and black lettering - Front: UNITE FIGHT / Back: ILGWU (Box 7, Folder 5)
- T-shirt - White with a large union label - Front: Made in U.S.A. - International Ladies' Garment Workers Union / Back: ILGWU (Box 7, Folder 6)
- T-shirt - White with blue and red lettering - Front: UNITE! Against Sweatshops / Back: www.uniteunion.org (Box 7, Folder 7)
- T-shirt - White with blue and red lettering - Front: UNITE! Against Sweatshops / Back: www.uniteunion.org (Box 7, Folder 8)
- T-shirt - Red with black and red lettering - Front: UNITE HERE! (Box 7, Folder 9)
- T-shirt - Red with black and red lettering - picture of President Obama - Front: UNTIE HERE! For OBAMA (Box 7, Folder 10)
- UNITE! Pins and ribbons [ribbons are white with blue and red lettering UNITE!] (6 pieces) (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Swatches of brightly colored union label cloth (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Shopping bags - plastic, advertising UNITE (4 pieces) (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Book cover - 'Famous Dates in History"; "Weights and Measures" (Box 8, Folder 2)
- ILGWU folders, 3 two pocket folders, bright yellow with a Union Label on the front (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire - Key chains (3 pieces) (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Post cards - Triangle Fire - (4 pieces), 2012 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- ILGWU - sewing kit; ruler (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Recognition Certificate - from Workers United Education Program (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Pins - (3) - We Are All Workers; (1) - Savethegarmentcenter.com; (1) - Political Activist UNITE! (Box 8, Folder 8)